Preston Scott

Lead Frontend and Backend Web Developer and SEO service provider

Mar Vista, CA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Preston-Scott/b8f415f098755c77

As owner of West Coast eCommerce, I have an 11 year history in providing high end eCommerce and SEO Services to

companies of all scales. I have excellent critical thinking and problem solving skills.

References and examples of work available upon request

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Frontend and Backend Web Developer and SEO service provider

Tauriga Sciences - May 2014 to June 2016

for this public company. Effectively produced a profitable ecommerce website and developed SEO plan that maximized profits for this company.

CTO

mCig inc - April 2014 to December 2015

April 2014 - December 2015

Developed a Highly functional Wordpress ecommerce Website for this public company. Developed an aggressive Search

Engine Optimization and social media marketing platform which brought this companies monthly income from \$25,000

a month to \$85,000 a month in three months. I was appointed CTO of this company in April of 2015.

Executive Drafts

- February 2014 to December 2015

Developed a Wordpress ecommerce Website for this digital service provider. Received a Forbes mention for this

website as being one of the top ten websites to jumpstart your career.

Lead Web Developer

Pro Sports Inc - November 2012 to December 2013

on both of this public companies asp.net websites. Involved efficient communication with the CEO,

COO, and CFO of this company and made use of my excellent critical thinking and problem solving skills to efficiently

implement website changes and orienting the website experience to be more user friendly.

Owner of West Coast eCommerce

West Coast eCommerce - 2006 to 2006

formerly SantaBarbaraWebDesign.net) an E-Commerce and SEO service oriented web design firm located in southern California.

EDUCATION

General Education and Multimedia Classes

Santa Barbara City College 2005

Santa Barbara High School 2000 to 2004